Businesses and Professions Collection 0007.002.004
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
Businesses and Professions
1920-2004
0007.002.004
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
4.5 Cubic feet 4 Boxes of collection records 5 boxes of photographs
This collection consists of newspaper clippings, advertisements, and memorabilia documenting the activities of Jewish business people and Jewish professionals (physicians, attorneys, artists, musicians, etc.) throughout the Hartford area.
Cohn, Philip, Restauranteur, (Cohn, Philip “Speedy”), b.1912/8/18, 304 Market St., Hartford, CT; Savitt, Frank, Jeweler; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Artist; Businesses & Professions -- Attorney; Businesses & Professions -- Butcher; Businesses & Professions -- Contractor; Businesses & Professions -- Fireman; Businesses & Professions -- Furrier; Businesses & Professions -- Journalist; Businesses & Professions -- Judge, Legal; Businesses & Professions -- Nurse; Businesses & Professions -- Pharmacist; Businesses & Professions -- Restauranteur; Businesses & Professions-- Physician; Businesses - Coal; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Appliances; Businesses -- Barber Shop; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors; Businesses -- Dairy; Businesses -- Delicatessen; Businesses -- Farming; Businesses -- Fishmarket; Businesses -- Fruit & Produce; Businesses -- Furnaces and Stoves; Businesses -- Furniture; Businesses -- Grocery; Businesses -- Meat Distributors; Businesses -- Music; Businesses -- Pharmacies; Businesses -- Shoe repair
- Series I: Businesses Advertising-Laundry
  Businesses & Professions
  - Businesses/Advertising and Public Relations, 1993; newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant and the Connecticut Jewish Ledger featuring stories on Jerome Lowengard.
    Lowengard, Jerome; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Advertising
  - Businesses/Ambulances, 1980s-1990s; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant, including a photocopy of the 1983 article "Harvey's Way".
    Harvey's Way
    Photocopy of the September 25, 1983 Hartford Courant article "Harvey's Way". The original resides in Oversize/Business/Misc.
    Kagan, Harvey L., Ambulance magnate; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Ambulances; Businesses -- Medical; Businesses -- Transportation
  - Businesses/Automobiles, 1904-1994; newspaper clippings; Wald, David (Box 1)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition note
    Copies of receipts for Nathan Burres, c. 1904, donated by his grandson Mr. David Wald in November, 1991.
    100 Years of the Automobile
    Contains a photocopy of the 1985 Classified Advertising Supplement to the Hartfourd Courant, "100 Years of the Automobile", whose original resides in Oversize/Business/Misc.
    Contains newspaper articles and obituaries from the Hartford Courant, the Hartford Jewish Ledger, the Connecticut Jewish Ledger, and Imprint Newspapers. Contains a photocopy of the 1985 Classified Advertising Supplement to the Hartfourd Courant, "100 Years of the Automobile", whose original resides in Oversize/Business/Misc. Also contains copies of invoice forms for Nathan Burres, Dr., for "Carriages, Wagons and General Jobbng. Horse Shoeing and Auto Repairing A Specialty."
    Burres, Nathan, Dr., Vilna; Goralnick, H. Robert, "Gorin", Automobile dealer, d. 1994, West Hartford, CT; Business Receipts; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Medical; Businesses -- Transportation
  - Businesses/Automobiles/Acme Auto Supply (Fine, Jim and Marsha), 1980s-1990s; Newspaper clippings; Fine, Marsha (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant and the Hartford Jewish Ledger regarding Melvin and James Fine.
    Fine, James L., Acme Auto Supply, Inc.; Fine, Melvin, Acme Auto Supply; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Transportation
  - Businesses/Bakery and Desserts/David Glass, 1980s-2000s, 1980-2009; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains articles from The Hartford Courant, the Connecticut Jewish Ledger, Lifestyles Magazine, Connecticut LIFE, and a photocopy of the 1989 Hartford Courant Northeast Magazine article "Sweet David Glass", whose original resides in Oversize/Business/Misc.
    Glass, David, Chocolatier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Baker; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Bakeries; Businesses -- Wholesale
  - Businesses/Bakery and Desserts/Eagle Bakery, 1930s, 1931; advertisement on program for Parsons Theatre production of "Uncle Moses" on May 4, 1931.; Eagle Bakery. (Box 1)
    File contains a program for the May 4, 1931 Parsons Theatre production of "Uncle Moses". The program includes an advertisement for the Eagle Bakery.
    Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Baker; Businesses -- Bakeries
  - Businesses/Banking, 1920s; credit ledger from 1920s; newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Contains one 1920s credit ledger. Also contains newspaper articles pertaining to banking in Hartford from The Hartford Courant and the Connecticut Jewish Ledger.
    1920s credit ledger from Pallotti, Andretta & Co.
    Leather-bound credit ledger stamped Pallotti, Andretta & Co. Bankers, Hartford, Connecticut. Signature of account holder appears to read M. P. Meister.
    Gerber, Murray A., President, Prototype & Plastic Mold; Shulansky, Ralph M., State banking commissioner; Silvers, Brett, Banker; Businesses & Professions -- Banker; Businesses -- Banks
  - Businesses/Banking/Society for Savings, 1969; Book publication w/ photos; Society for Savings, The. (Hartford, CT) (Box 1)
    This folder contains a 1968 publication created by the Society for Savings, entitled "Passbook to a Proud Past and a Promising Future". This publication contains a substantial amount of material, including photographs, pertaining to the history of Hartford and the Society for Savings branch operations.
    Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Banks; Hartford history
  - Businesses/Beauty and Hairdressing/Beauty Enterprises (Robert Cohen), 1980s-1990s, 1980-1999; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from the University of Hartford Observer and the Connecticut Jewish Ledger, and photocopied articles from The Hartford Courant featuring stories about Robert Cohen, President of Beauty Enterprises.
    Beauty Enterprises, Inc..; Cohen, Robert H., President, Beauty Enterprises of Hartford; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Barber Shop; Businesses -- Beauty Salon
  - Businesses/Bedding, 1987-1997; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles and photocopies thereof from the Hartford Courant and the Connecticut Jewish Ledger, and a photocopy of an advertisement for "three d Bed & Bath".
    Separated Materials note
    Contains a photocopy of an advertisement for "three d Bed & Bath" whose original resides in Oversize/Business/Misc.
    Naboicheck, N. Aaron, Standard Mattress Co.; Naboicheck, Robert J., Standard Mattress Co.; Standard Mattress Co..; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail
  - Businesses/Boating, 1986; Newspaper clipping
    Contains one newspaper clipping featuring a photo of Norman Kurtz, a Boston Whaler dealer, receiving an award for Top 50 Dealer of 1985.
    Norman Marine.
  - Businesses/Books/H. Walfish Book Dealer/copy of Grace and Blessings for Various Occasions, 1915 with H. Walfish stamp in English and Hebrew, Copy of Grace and Blessings for Various Occasions, 1915, in sleeve; H. Walfish Book Dealer. (Box 1)
    1915 copy of Grace and Blessings for Various Occasions, in English and Hebrew, with H. Walfish Book Deaker stamp.
    Businesses & Professions -- Bookseller; Religious Life; Religious objects
  - Businesses/Books/Huntington's Book Store, 1835-1993; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles and obituaries from the Jewish Ledger and The Hartford Courant, featuring the life and work of Issac Epstein, owner of Huntington's [bookstore].
    Epstein, David, Bookseller; Epstein, Isaac, Bookseller, d. 1988; Huntington's Book Store.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Bookseller; Businesses - Retail
  - Businesses/ Building Supplies/ American Mason & Building Supply Co., undated; newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Folder contains newspaper article from the Hartford Courant featuring the business, American Masons Supply Co. and it's owners Efrem Jaffe and Joel Cohen.
    American Mason's and Building Supply Company.; Cohen, Joel, Building supplies; Jaffe, Efrem, Building supplies; Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Building Supplies
  - Businesses/Cleaners, undated; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles and clippings from the Connecticut Jewish Ledger, the Hartford Jewish Ledger, and The Hartford Courant featuring stories on Fred and Regina Jacobs and the business Dan-Dee Cleaners. Also an article discussing the 40th anniversary of Esquire Cleaners and its original owner Emil Ellenberg.
    Ellenberg, Emil, Business Owner; Jacobs, Fred; Jacobs, Regina; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Laundry Services
  - Businesses/Clothing/A. Katten & Son, 1918; Photocopy
    File contains a photocopy of a 1918 letter from Myron Katten to Mr. Max L. Goldenthal regarding proposals to build a Jewish Hospital.
    A. Katten & Son Hartford One Price Clothing Co..; Katten, Myron, Clothier; Hospitals; Mount Sinai Hospital
  - Businesses/Clothing/Abe's Fashions, 1995; Newspaper clipping
    Contains a newspaper article from The Hartford Courant (Dec. 14, 1995) featuring charitable works of store owner Abe Tsarfaty.
    Abe's Fashions.; Tsarfaty, Abe, Clothier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Bassok's Clothing Store, undated (Box 1)
  - Businesses/Clothing/Bazilian's, 2002; Newspaper clippings w/ photos (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant and the Connecticut Jewish Ledger featuring stories on Bazilian's clothing store on Park Road in Hartford, CT and its owner, Marc Bazilian. Bazilian's, originally located on Front Street and was founded in 1930 by Joseph M. Bazilian, an immigrant from Vilna.
    Bazilian's.; Bazilian, Joseph M., Vilna; Bazilian, Marc, Clothier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors; Front Street, Hartford, CT
  - Businesses/Clothing/Bob's Stores Inc., 1990s-2000s; Newspaper clippings; Internet printout (Box 1)
    Contains an obituary and death notice for Bob Lapidus, as well as an article about his retirement, from The Hartford Courant.
    Bob's Stores, Inc.. (Middletown, CT); Lapidus, Robert Jacob, Clothier, 1929 - 2007, Turner Falls, MA; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Casual Corner, 1950-1999; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains an op-ed piece from the West Hartford News featuring the success story of Charlie Carples, owner of the franchise store, Causal Corners.
    Carples, Charles, Clothier, d. 1990; Casual Corner.; U.S. Shoe Corp..; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Costumes/Fierberg: See People Files/Fierberg, undated (Box 1)
  - Businesses/Clothing/Custom and Special Services, 1980-1999; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains a photocopy of The Hartford Courant's February 1990 Business Weekly, "Blood, Sweaters and Tears", whose original resides in Oversize/Business/Clothing.
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant, the West Hartford News, and the Jewish Ledger, including a photocopy of The Hartford Courant's February 1990 Business Weekly, "Blood, Sweaters and Tears".
    Businesses & Professions; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors; Businesses -- Importers
  - Businesses/Clothing/Florence Travis/The Gilded Cage, 1996; newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant and the West Hartford News featuring the story of the Florence Travis clothing store.
    Florence Travis.; Gilded Cage, The.; Travis, William, Clothier; Zieky, Sandy, Clothier; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Furriers, 1980s; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant featuring stories on Lerner's Furs Inc. (owner Arthur W. Lerner of Middletown, CT) and the 59th anniversary of the Connecticut Furriers of New Britain (Joseph Rubenstein, founder and President).
    Connecticut Furriers of New Britain.; Lerner, Arthur W., Furrier; Rubenstein, Joseph, Furrier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Furrier; Businesses - Retail; S. Max & Co Fur Shop
  - Businesses/Clothing/Gillman Shop, 1995; Newspaper clipping
    Contains a newspaper clipping from the Jewish Ledger featuring story on the 100th birthday of Samuel M. Gillman, proprietor of the Gillman Shop on Pratt Street in Hartford, CT..
    Gillman Shop, The.; Gillman, Samuel, Clothier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Haberdasher/Mintz & Levin, undated; letter and transcription of same; Warner, Hilda Levin (Box 1)
    Contains a handwritten letter regarding Bernard David Lepin, and a typed transcription thereof, written by his daughter, Hilda Warner.
    Bernard Mintz, Haberdasher; Levin, Bernard David, Haberdasher; Mintz & Levin.; Business & Professions -- Haberdasher; Businesses & Professions
  - Businesses/Clothing/Harmac Clothiers for Men, 1960s-1991, Newspaper clipping w/ photo (Box 1)
    Contains one newspaper article from the West Hartford News featuring the closing of Harmac Clothiers after 35 years in business in the Hartford area.
    Harmac Clothiers for Men.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/J. R. Pollack, 1960-1989; Newspaper clippings w/ photos (Box 1)
    Contains a newspaper article and a photocopy thereof from the West Hartford News featuring a story on J & R Pollack Men's and Women's Clothing store, and its owner, Robert Pollack.
    J & R Pollack Men's and Women's Clothing Store.; Pollack, Joseph, Clothier; Pollack, Robert, Clothier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Keene's Sports Shop/Sports Center, 1998; Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Contains Hartford Courant obituary of Herb Sheintop.
    Sheintop, Herb, Clothier, d. 1998; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors; Sports
  - Businesses/Clothing/Miscellaneous, 1860s-2000s; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains photocopies of newspaper obituary of William B. Rothschild. Contains newspaper clipping from the Connecticut Jewish Ledger.
    Rothschild, William B., Haberdasher; Business & Professions -- Haberdasher; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Modern Woman, 1984; Newspaper clipping w/ photo (Box 1)
    Contains a newspaper article from the West Hartford News featuring a story on the closing of Modern Woman, one of the oldest businesses on LaSalle Road.
    Katz, Gertrude, Business Owner; Modern Woman.; Schwartz, Nan, Business owner; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors; LaSalle Road, Hartford CT
  - Businesses/Clothing/Needlework/The Wool Collection, 1996; Newspaper clippings w/ photo (Box 1)
    Contains a newspaper article from The Hartord Courant featuring a story on the 'Wool Connection', an Avon business owned by Phyllis Fishberg.
    Fishberg, Phyllis, Clothier; Wool Connection, The.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Regal Men's Shop, 1940s-2000s, 1940-2000; Newspaper clipping w/ photo (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper article (10/16/2000) from The Hartford Courant featuring a story on the closing of the Regal Men's Shop and its owners, the Apter family.
    Apter, Bernard, Clothier; Apter, Louis, Clothier; Regal's Men's Shop.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Sam's Army Navy, 1920s-1990s, 1920-1990s; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper article from The Hartford Courant featuring story on Leo Bachner, owner of Sam's Army and Navy Store on Trumbull Street.
    Bachner, Leo; Bachner, Sam; Sam's Army and Navy Store.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Security Uniforms, 1990s-2000s; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant featuring stories about Security Uniforms on Broad Street in New Britain.
    Gottlieb, Ross, Outfitter; Gottlieb, Sy, Outfitter; Security Uniforms.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Fireman; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors; Businesses -- Outfitters; CT Police/State Troopers; New Britain, CT
  - Businesses/Clothing/Shoes, 1950s-1980s; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles and obituaries from The Hartford Courant and the Jewish Ledger. Contains photocopy of a Hartford Courant advertisement for Kofsky Shoe Stores from 1955.
    Kofsky Shoe Stores.; Kofsky, Bernard; Kofsky, George M., d. 1987; Tru-Balance Shoes.; Zelman, Arthur, Outfitter; Zelman, Sandy, Outfitter; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Siegal Shop, 1920s-1980s, 1920-1988; Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper article from the West Hartford News featuring story on Bernard Matlaw and his retirement after 40 years in the fashion industry.
    Matlaw, Bernard, Clothier; Matlaw, Doris; Siegel Shop.; Siegel, Abraham, Clothier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Tailors/Merin, Samuel, 1920s-1980s, 1981; Newspaper clipping w/photo (Box 1)
    Contains one newspaper article featuring story on clothing tailor, Samuel Merin.
    Merin, Samuel; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Tailor; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors; Holocaust survivors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Udolf's, 1929-2000, Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Contains one newspaper article from The Hartford Courant featuring story on Leonard Udolf, owner of Udolf's Clothiers.
    Udolf's Clothiers.; Udolf, Eli, Clothier; Udolf, Leonard, Clothier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Weathervane, 1998-2004; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant featuring story on the liquidation and bankruptcy of New Britain's clothing retailer, Weathervane.
    Weathervane.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Clothing/Weiner's Clothiers, 1927-1990s, 1997; Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper article from The Hartford Courant Business section on Weiner's Clothiers, a Newington store owned by Charles Weiner.
    Weiner's Clothiers.; Weiner, Charles, Clothier; Weiner, Julius, Tailor; Weiner, Nathan, Clothier; Weiner, Rick, Clothier; Businesses & Professions; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Clothing/Tailors
  - Businesses/Coffee/Baronet Gourmet Coffee, 1991-1993; Newspaper and magazine clippings (Box 1)
    Contains one newspaper article from The Hartford Courant and one magazine article from Connecticut Magazine featuring stories on Baronet Gourmet Coffee, located on Weston Street in Hartford.
    Baronet Gourmet Coffee.; Goldsmith, Bruce, Coffee roaster; Goldsmith, Isadore, Coffee roaster; Goldsmith, Leon, Coffee roaster; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Coffee; Businesses -- Importers; Businesses -- Wholesale
  - Businesses/Computers, 2000; Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from the Connecticut Jewish Ledger featuring a story on Morton Handel and his employment as CEO of Concurrent Computer Corp. Also, a Ledger article on the 'Y2K Panic'.
    Handel, Morton; Pratt & Whitney.; Businesses & Professions -- Computers
  - Businesses/Construction, 1980s-1990s; Newspaper clippings, photocopies (Box 1)
    Related Archival Materials note
    Contains a note to see Individuals & Families Vertical File/Savin Family.
    Contains newspaper articles and obituaries from The Hartford Courant and the Connecticut Jewish Ledger. Includes a note to see, for more information, Individuals & Families Vertical File/Savin Family.
    Beckenstein Enterprises.; Beckenstein, Henry, Builder, d. 1996; T & M Builders.; Temkin, Steven, Builder; Businesses & Professions -- Builders
  - Businesses/Consumer Electronics, 1990s; Newspaper clippings, photocopies (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles from The Hartford Courant. Contains a photocopy of the Business Weekly 1997 article "Endangered Species: When expert repair people retire, who will fill their shoes?", the original residing in Oversize.
    Contains a photocopy of the Business Weekly 1997 article "Endangered Species: When expert repair people retire, who will fill their shoes?", the original residing in Oversize.
    Antar, Eddie, Consumer Electronics; Beacon Light & SupplyCo..; Bernie's.; Cohen, Benjamin, Electronics Repair; Cohen, Rebecca, Electronics Repair; Crazy Eddie Inc.; Singer, Benjamin, Electrical Engineer, d. 1995; Supreme Radio & TV.; Businesses & Professions; Businesses & Professions -- Computers; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Consumer Electronics
  - Businesses/Department Stores, D & L, Bulk, 1980-1994; undated; Newspaper clippings. 1986 75th Anniversary Celebration cataog. Glossy printed photographs and copies of newspaper stories. Credit cards. (Box 1)
    Contains newspaper articles, original and photocopied, from The Hartford Courant, and glossy prints of Courant stories and photographs. Also contains 75th Anniversary D & L catalog and D & L credit cards.
    D & L Department Stores.; Davidson, Lawrence Jr.; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Department Stores
  - Businesses/Department Stores/G. Fox & Co., undated (Box 1)
  - Businesses/Department Stores/Horwitz, 1920s-1990s, 1992; Photocopies of newspaper articles (Box 1)
    This file contains a photocopy of an October 5, 1992 Hartford Courant Business Weekly article about Horwitz department stores closing. The original is located in Oversize/Business/Clothing.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    The original October 5, 1992 Hartford Courant Business Weekly article is located in Oversize/Business/Clothing.
    Horwitz Inc..; Horwitz, Paul; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Department Stores
  - Businesses/Department Stores/Levy & Mayer, undated; Photocopy of article (Box 1)
    File contains a photocopy of an article, "Tales of Two Heroes", reprinted in The Jewish Veteran from the Springfield Daily News.
    Karpeles, Leopold, Sgt.; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Department Stores
  - Businesses/Department Stores/Sage Allen, undated; One charge card from Sage-Allen & Co. (Box 1)
    This file contains one plastic charge card from Sage-Allen & Co., bearing the signature of Lillian B. Marlow.
  - Businesses/Department Stores/Shapiro's, September 21, 1995; Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    File contains a newspaper clipping of the Hartford Courant obituary for Bertha Shapiro.
    Shapiro, Bertha, d. 9/19/1995; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Department Stores
  - Businesses/Department Stores/Wal-mart, April 11, 2003; Newspaper clipping (Box 1)
    File contains a newspaper clipping from the Jewish Ledger regarding Wal-mart in Avon beginning to stock Passover goods.
    Wal-mart.; Businesses - Retail; Businesses -- Department Stores
  - Businesses/Directories/West Hartford Book, 2008-2009 Edition, West Hartford Book, 2008-2009 Edition.
    File contains one copy of the 2008-2009 West Hartford Book.